Will he save their world... or destroy it?
Planet Hulk is a science fiction, animation, action film directed by Sam Liu.
When the Hulk's presence on Earth becomes too great a risk, the Illuminati trick him to board a shuttle
destined for a planet where he will be able to live in peace, and launch it into space.
The Hulk's struggle to escape causes the shuttle to malfunction and crash land on the planet
Sakaar, however, where he is sold into slavery and trained as a gladiator.
Hulk (voice), played by Rick D. Wasserman.
Caiera (voice), played by Lisa Ann Beley.
Red King (voice), played by Mark Hildreth.
Hiroim (voice), played by Liam O'Brien.
Korg (voice), played by Kevin Michael Richardson.
Miek (voice), played by Sam Vincent.
"Planet Hulk" is a Marvel Comics storyline that ran primarily
through issues of The Incredible Hulk starting in 2006.
Written by Greg Pak, it dealt with the Marvel heroes' decision to send the Hulk away, his acclimation to and
conquest of the planet where he landed, Sakaar, and his efforts to return to Earth to take his revenge.
There was also a special Planet Hulk: Gladiator Guidebook publication by Anthony Flamini and the storyline's main writer Greg Pak,
similar to the Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe detailing the characters, races and cultures within the storyline.
Elements from the storyline have been adapted into other media, including an animated
film of the same name, as well as the live action film Thor: Ragnarok.
The film explores themes of rebellion, superhero,
illuminati, based on comic, superhuman strength.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.